JS 02

Kisi bh Programing main Core Fandamentals 5 Hote Hain
1)Variables, 2)Loop, 3)Conditions, 4)Array, 5)Functions

VARIABLES: 
Values Save Krne ke lye 
Jab Bh Data Save KRna 

A variable is any property, characteristic, number, or quantity that increases or
decreases over time or can take on different values (as opposed to constants, such 
as n, that do not vary) in different situations. When conducting research, experiments 
often manipulate variables.

Variable main Data Save krte hain
Data 5 Types ke Hpte hain
1)String
2)Number
3)Boolean
4)Null
5)Undefined
